https://www.sedere.com/terms-of-use/

TERMS OF USE————–These Terms and Conditions of Use (these “Terms of Use”) apply to the SEDERE website located at www.sedere.com and all associated sites. The Site is the property of SEDERE SAS. (“we”) and its licensors. BY USING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO THESE TERMS OF USE; IF YOU DO NOT AGREE, DO NOT USE THE SITE.SEDERE SAS reserves the right, at its discretion, to modify any portions of those Terms of Use, at any time. It is your responsibility to check these Terms of Use periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes will mean that you accept and agree to the changes. As long as you comply with these Terms of Use, SEDERE grants you a personal, non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited privilege to enter and use the Site.ContentAll text, graphics, interfaces, photographs, trademarks, logos and artworks (collectively, “Content”), including but not limited to the design, structure, selection, coordination, expression, “look and feel” and arrangement of such Content, contained on the Site is owned, controlled or licensed by or to SEDERE SAS, and is protected by copyright, patent and trademark laws.Except as expressly provided in these Terms of Use, no part of the Site and no Content may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, publicly displayed, encoded, translated, transmitted or distributed in any way (including “mirroring”) to any other computer, server, website or other medium for publication or distribution or for any commercial enterprise, without SEDERE’s express prior written consent.You may use information on SEDERE SAS products (such as datasheets, brochures, application notes and similar) purposely made available by SEDERE SAS for downloading from the Site, provided that you (1) not remove any proprietary notice language in all copies of such documents, (2) make no modifications to any such information, and (3) not make any additional representations or warranties relating to such documents.You may not attempt to access without authority, interfere with, damage or disrupt: any part of our site, any equipment or network on which our site is stored, any software used in the provision of our site or any equipment or network or software owned or used by any third party.You may not use the Site or any Content for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms of Use, or to solicit the performance of any illegal activity or other activity which infringes the rights of SEDERE SAS or others.Links to Other Sites and to the SEDERE websiteThis Site may contain links to other independent third-party websites (“Linked Sites”). These Linked Sites are provided solely as a convenience to our visitors. Such Linked Sites are not under SEDERE’s control, and SEDERE SAS is not responsible for and does not endorse the content of such Linked Sites, including any information or materials contained on such Linked Sites. You will need to make your own independent judgment regarding your interaction with these Linked Sites.Your Personal InformationsWhen you contact SEDERE via this Site you will be asked to provide personally identifying contact information (e.g., name, organization, address, phone number, e-mail address, and so on) and other informations. From time to time, we may use contact information obtained via this Site to send e-mail and postal mail supplying customers with the most recent product and service information as well as other information we think may be useful to you.Third partiesWe may share information about you with employees, affiliates, successors, and agents, representatives or distributors, which are required to treat the information in accordance with our Terms. Except as specifically described in these Terms, we will not, without your specific prior consent, sell, trade or transfer your information to unaffiliated third parties other than authorized third parties (such as, for example, contractors supporting operation of this Site) and others involved in the e-commerce distribution chain (e.g., vendors, service providers), which may need access to some of your personal information. We oblige such third parties to comply with our Terms, and limit their access and use of your personal information.DISCLAIMERPlease read carefully as this clause limits your ability to claim damages.The main purpose of the Website is to provide information to users in relation to the products that SEDERE SAS manufactures and promotes.SEDERE makes every effort to check the accuracy of information published on the Website. You should note however that SEDERE does not give any warranty that any information will be accurate or up-to-date and the user acknowledges that the information and services offered on the Website is offered on an “as is” basis. In particular, and without limitation to the rest of this agreement, SEDERE is not able to guarantee that its service will continue or be accurate during time of server failure.Information contained in, or accessible via, the Website changes on a regular basis. SEDERE may make improvements or alterations to the Website at any time and without notice. SEDERE is not responsible in any way whatsoever for the content of any site accessed using the Website, nor can it warrant that use of the Website will be free from virus contamination and you should take adequate steps to ensure that you virus check regularly when using the Website on any device.SEDERE makes no representations about the suitability of the information and services contained on, or accessed via, the Website for any purpose. All warranties, terms and conditions with regard to this information and services, including all warranties, terms and conditions, implied by statute, collaterally or otherwise, of satisfactory quality, fitness for a particular purpose, title, and non-infringement are excluded to the fullest extent permitted by law.SEDERE shall not in any event be liable for any damages (whether indirect, incidental, special, consequential or otherwise) arising out of, or in any way connected with, the use of the Website, or with any delayed access to, or inability to use the Website, or for any information and services obtained through the Website, or otherwise arising out of the use of the Website, whether based on contract, tort, strict liability or otherwise, even if SEDERE has been advised of the possibility of damages. This does not affect the statutory rights of any person dealing as a consumer nor shall anything in these terms and conditions exclude or limit liability for death or personal injury caused by negligence or for fraudulent misrepresentation.Limitation of LiabilityExcept where prohibited by law, in no event will SEDERE SAS be liable to you for any indirect, consequential, exemplary, incidental or punitive damages, including lost profits, even if SEDERE SAS has been advised of the possibility of such damages.If, notwithstanding the other provisions of these Terms of Use, SEDERE SAS is found to be liable to you for any damage or loss which arises out of or is in any way connected with your use of the Site or any Content, SEDERE’s liability shall in no event exceed 100 Euros (one hundred euros). Some jurisdictions do not allow limitations of liability, so the foregoing limitation may not apply to you.IndemnityYou agree to indemnify and hold SEDERE SAS, its officers, directors, shareholders, predecessors, successors in interest, employees, agents, subsidiaries and affiliates, harmless from any demands, loss, liability, claims or expenses (including attorneys’ fees), made against SEDERE by any third party due to or arising out of or in connection with your use of the Site.Violation of These Terms of UseSEDERE may disclose any information we have about you (including your identity) if we determine that such disclosure is necessary in connection with any investigation or complaint regarding your use of the Site, or to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) SEDERE’s rights or property, or the rights or property of visitors to or users of the Site, including SEDERE’s customers.The information contained in this website is subject to change without notice.SEDERE SAS, Parc Volta, BP10027, 9 rue Parmentier, 94141 ALFORTVILLE CEDEX – Franceemail: info(at)sedere.comlast revision of those terms : April 10th 2020This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessaryAny cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
Français
